(Sheldon:)The white zone
is for loading and unloading.
(Sheldon:)We're breaking the law.
(Penny:)- There's no space in the white zone, so...
- Anyway...
(Leonard:)...we can e-mail and I think
the phone connections are good.
You have to get out of the car now.
I'm not going to jail.
- Would you just relax?
- Oh, I see a space in the white zone.
(Sheldon:)Quick, circle the airport.
- Did you bring enough inhalers?
- Yeah.
And extra Dramamine? You remember
what happened on It's a Small World.
- I'm covered.
- Okay.
(Sheldon:)Dear Lord, a police officer
is glancing in our direction.
(Sheldon:)We've been made.
(Leonard:)Calm down, I'm getting out.
(Leonard:)- I have something I want to give you.
- Oh, Leonard.
It's a locket with Leonard's face in it.
(Sheldon:)He got it at the mall on clearance.
Move, move, move!
(Penny:)I love you.
(Leonard:)I love you too.
(Sheldon:)Don't worry, officer, they just love
each other, we're not smuggling drugs.